[{"answer": "Well, in my mind it is, because the state really didn't have any valid evidence to go on.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "In the end, was it the lack of forensic evidence which you think led to this acquittal?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "No, and that was one of the problems that the prosecution had is there was no cause of death.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "From everything that you saw, from everything that you examined, did you ever see evidence of premeditated murder?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "You know, I really don't want to speculate.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "I mean, do you have any personal feeling about what you think happened to her?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "EICHS: Well, one of the things that forensic anthropologists look for is manner of death or cause of death.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "But did you see anything -- when you examined Caylee's remains, did you see anything that would go along with that theory, that would corroborate it in any way?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "On the other hand, it's been a hell of an ordeal for them, and if she is innocent, as this jury has decided that she is, you can understand that explosion of emotion at the end, can't you?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "You're always surprised at verdicts in cases like this.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "I mean, from a legal point of view, were you surprised at the verdict?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's fringe science.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "You are so right, Piers, and everybody in America and all over the world who are following this know that in their gut, in their heart of hearts, people are upset about this verdict.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "So there are some very big unanswered questions here, aren't there?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, to tell you the truth, it's really not like that because there was predictions that we were going to lose this case or at least not be able to convict from long before we even started to pick the jury because of a variety of issues including celebrity, race, the Rodney King riots.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "What is that moment like when you realize that it's going against all popular thought and actually you're going to lose the case?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I'm very proud that we have the First Amendment here in America and we can shine the light on all three of our branches of government -- legislative, executive, and judicial.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Is this not the problem with having cameras in these courtrooms?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, if you want truth, get scientists.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "I mean if a legal system isn't based on truth and justice, then what kind of system is it?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "On Thursday is her sentencing.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What happens to Casey Anthony next?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Lisa Bloom, Marcia -- oh, go on.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "But explain why a skilled attorney would raise an issue of abuse?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I'm just wondering why a skilled attorney would raise allegations which he couldn't prove of sexual abuse by the father of the daughter.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Alan?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, I actually predicted the best-case scenario for the defense would be a hung jury.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Did you predict this not guilty verdict?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, it can.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "I mean, can the results of these cases literally fall down on one or two or three jurors and the selection process?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, we didn't really focus on the demographics.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Do you think that was help informal the end to Casey Anthony?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Very quickly, we don't have star chamber justice in this country.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Why do you need them?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I don't think they do.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "I mean, how on Earth does this family even attempt to rebuild any kind of relationship here, given what went on in the courtroom?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "That I wasn't that surprised.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "What was your gut feeling when that verdict came in?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I have not encountered that specific experience, but I've encountered -- this case -- Casey reminds me of several of my patients, frankly.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "But, Drew, listen, I take that point, but have you ever in your entire career come across a mother who has lost a child and doesn't report that for 31 days?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Probably, Piers.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Brad Conway, finally, do you agree with Dr. Drew that there's really no way back for this family, in terms of any relationship between the parents and their daughter?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "When it's high profile, when it's famous, predicting a verdict is almost impossible, isn't it?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "You're right, Piers.", "docId": "110705pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "But what didn't make any sense either -- and I keep coming back to this -- is what kind of mother who loses a child doesn't report it for more than a month?", "qSentId": 591}]